Hey y'all.
I'm back. I had the rush here. I was
just trying to reup on my drink and I
was just like, "Oh my god, it's 10:15
already."
Geez.
But yeah, welcome to another episode of
Pop Quicky. Like where I do some quick
hot topics. Y'all have been sending me
that video with Amanda Seals, child. I
was just like, let me just speak on this
right quick. Um, before we get into the
mess and the pettiness, y'all, we are
sold out. We are [ __ ] sold out.
The first live show of Pop Roast is
officially sold out at the Green Room
42.
H, feels so good. It feels good.
It feels good.
Oh my god.
Thank y'all so much for the support. We
appreciate y'all so much. And if y'all
want to watch our very first live show.
Um the link to the live stream of the
show, it's in the description below. The
beauty of the live stream is you get to
keep that live stream for seven days. So
you don't even have to uh watch the show
live. you can just buy the live stream
ticket and watch it when you want
between seven days. So yeah, it's in the
description um below if you you know if
you can't make it or you know it's sold
out.
Anyway, um oh also I might have an extra
free ticket because someone emailed me
saying that they couldn't make it to the
show.
Now, if someone wants to DM me on my
Instagram, CDiggi1, if you want to come
in person and you're serious, let me
know and I will see if that person can
just transfer their ticket. All right,
anywh who, let's get into these hot
topics, shall we? So, Amanda Seals uh
got on her Instagram
uh to do a little like one of those
little Netflix um what do you call it?
It's like it's trending where you know
they have the little violin in the
background
where they like do the documentary
exposing stuff and it's basically like
her as Tiffany Dubois
saying that why she isn't on the
Insecure tour and I'm just like first
and foremost
it's petty and I didn't mind it. I
didn't mind it at all. But the thing is,
don't lead people on to the fact that
you weren't asked to to join. Like,
there's a reason why you're not a part
of this. And we all know. I just don't
want people to think that like they're
shutting her out. Like, cut the
revisionist history [ __ ] There's a
reason that she's not a part of the uh
anniversary tour. But yeah, uh let me
show y'all if you missed it.
Let's see.
Uh, of course things want to Let's see.
There we go.
>> It's fine. It's fine.
>> She got some sort of wig put on
and I thought it was a cute little joke.
But yeah, it says Tiffany Dwine Netflix
doc about not being on the insecure
tour. Like girl, we know why you not on
the insecure tour. Like you talk [ __ ]
about the creator, you talk [ __ ] about
the boss. Like she's known for being
difficult to work with. And I'm just
like, why would people want like why
would Issa and them want to deal with
that? And I get it. It sucks that the
whole cast can't be together because
it's literally all of them except for
Amanda. And it just is what it is, you
know?
Exactly. Don't f with the boss or you
might just get fired. Luckily, she
didn't get fired from the show. And to
her credit, because I'm not a hater. I'm
not a hater at all. Like Amanda Sills is
talented, but just like Tamar, she's
known for something else more than her
talent, you know, and I do think that
she's funny at times. It's just she's
not the most pleasant person. And you
can be the most talented person in
Hollywood. If people don't want to work
with you, if you are not kind, it takes
nothing to be kind to somebody. Then it
just is what it is. But what really
annoyed me was it's like people in the
comments saying that like, "Oh, well,
she's been a part of this show, the
legacy and stuff like that. She needs to
be a part of the tour." Says who? Says
who. Exactly. Thank you, Max, for
reminding everybody
she was a co-host on The Real for one
season, and there was a reason for that.
Like everyone who has worked with Amanda
Seals, spoiler alert, they have a story,
you know,
and I feel like I am a nice person
and I get it. She blocked me for, you
know, um, doing that little Hot Topic
segment with Alex, but it is what it is.
She told me, "Choose better friends."
And I did. And I did. I'm doing a
soldout show with my friend who's still
with me to this day.
And yeah, I like let's not like pretend
like her role was like that
quintessential
like she was a plus one on the show too
if we keeping it a buck.
But yeah, like some people in the
comments, they're saying um
let me see. Uh
oh. Well, here's here's what some people
are saying. They're choosing peace and
don't want the headache. I don't blame
them. You don't fool with them, so why
would you expect to be involved? That's
the only thing. Like you can joke and do
a little Netflix doc parody thing, but
don't give people the impression that
you wanted to be a part of it or you're
shocked that you're not a part of it. I
think that's what that was the only
thing that annoyed me. And there were
some people who are her fans asking,
"Oh, well,
why is why aren't you a part of it,
Amanda? Why aren't you a part of it?"
And I'm just like,
did y'all watch the show? Tamar, did
y'all see what happened outside of the
production? Did y'all see like like when
Issa went on tour by herself and she was
interviewed, she said, "Well, if you
talking [ __ ] about me, of course I'm not
going to include you on anything else."
1 plus one equals two, y'all.
like I there's no other way I can really
explain it. And then I knew it kind of
burned her ego a little bit because she
posted something I believe soon as they
announced the Insecure tour. like I
think the day after or around the same
week she posted like old clips from the
insecure days and was just saying like
um
I guess like an anniversary post, but
I think she did that knowing that people
was going to ask well where are you on
the tour? Where were you on the tour?
And she was just like and she answered
somebody and said well I wasn't um asked
to be a part of it. Are you surprised by
that? That's my thing. And the thing is,
everyone is everyone else on the cast,
they're living well in abundance.
I just think when there's so many people
that have a problem with you, you got to
look in the mirror. Like,
I'm gonna start calling Amanda Seal
Shamia. They probably need to have a
talk together. Like, it can't be
everybody. It can't be everybody.
Now, I thought my situation with Amanda,
maybe that was just, you know, something
that like,
you know, maybe it was me or um
[laughter]
like, but when when I hear multiple
people are saying their different
stories, I'm like, well, well.
[laughter]
[gasps and sighs] Oh, thank y'all so
much for the congratulations. I I'm
really excited about the live show.
People act obtuse. Nobody wants to work
with a difficult colleague. Exactly. It
It's just that simple. And the only
reason that
I'm even talking about this story is
because a lot of people wanted my
opinion on it. As soon as I saw it, I
was like, "Oh, okay. That's a little
cute parody thing she did." But to lead
people on and gaslight them that like,
you know, she's the one that's being
shut out. I mean, there's a reason.
There's a reason.
Like, Google is free, y'all.
Let me see. Uh, there was something
else.
A lot of people are comparing it to, um,
Sex in the City with Samantha. Um,
I don't think we can compare Samantha's
character to
um,
Tiffany Dubois. I'm sorry. Samantha was
like a pivotal part of Sex in the City.
And she was also in every single
episode. Every single episode. Issa and
Molly and Jay Ellis, uh, Lawrence, they
were in every single episode. Natasha
Rothell,
uh, Kelly.
I mean, we love her. I mean, I will
protect Natasha Rothell at all cost. She
was a standout and stole many scenes.
And also, someone else uh tweeted
something that was really funny.
They compared it. Let me see. Uh, where
did I put it?
Oh my gosh. But yeah, someone said um
that's like um saying that well for the
next Destiny's Child reunion, we need we
need to invite Farah.
I was like not Farah.
Nah, Kim Catrol kept it classy and
didn't say a word unless she was
directly asked. It's just I hate that I
I was telling my friend this that every
iconic show just has that one little
stain. Now, I'm not calling Amanda Sils
a stain, but I'm just saying like just
every iconic
like show that we know of. I think you
can just point out something that was a
hiccup or a [ __ ] in the armor or
something like that.
Uh, Natasha also has White Lotus, too.
Farah is still looking for her luggage,
so she won't be able to attend.
Yes, Natasha also wrote a lot of
episodes for Insecure. Amanda can't
compare.
I didn't mean it like, y'all know what I
mean. Y'all know what I mean. I wasn't
calling her a stain. I'm just saying
every iconic show probably has just a
little a little stain in their long
trajectory and [ __ ] like that.
That's why reunions and reboots always
have one person missing. Exactly. And I
would love an Insecure movie. I would
love a Kelly spin-off.
But I just hope Amanda doesn't expect to
be in that movie. I hope not. Not even
as a cameo. Unless she does like maybe a
public apology or something like that.
So just stand in it. Just stand in it,
Amanda. Like you can have your fun.
You've had your fun. Let the mouse go
for real. Like and it just sucks that
you know they're celebrating. They
announced the tour and here she come
with her with her like her dark cloud
over it. So now you're going to have
some messy ass people. If there's a
question, if there's a Q&A portion of
the show, they're going to be asking,
"Where's Amanda?" And I'm just like,
"You dumb [ __ ] Wh what? Why?
Why? Why you think Amanda ain't there?"
And I hope they c I hope they embarrass
anybody that even ask why Amanda isn't
there?
Like if someone talks [ __ ] then they're
not going to be a part of it. It's just
that simple.
That simple,
right? Like why even go through the
headache even if they were extending it
to her?
Like I wonder, you know what? I wonder
if they did like in some multiverse if
they did extend that opportunity for
her, would she take it?
Probably. Maybe. or she would um turn it
down and let people know that she was
offered and she turned it down. I can
see her doing that.
Not Amanda got left out of bad and
bougie.
But yeah, she's allowed to speak on the
show. I'm not saying that. But just I
don't like it as like for her to
like give people the impression that she
was done wrong or she's being done
dirty. I think that's like that's just
not honest given the history that she
has with the show and the show's
creator. That's all I'm saying. She
could talk about the show and do a
little parody
anyway.
So, let's talk about the bomb that
dropped on Salt Lake City and all eyes
will be on next season. We have another
separation on the cast. It is Angie K
and her husband Shawn. They have
separated after 27
years.
27 years.
And then the initial report was just
like a like a uh like a rumor
and they were saying that there was
infidelity involved on Sea's part and
you know they they were saying it was a
stylist at the salon and they didn't
give the gender so everybody was asking
oh is was it a woman or a man
cuz I mean
I mean
I I mean,
how you doing? How you doing? You know,
I mean, I can I can see it, but I don't
want to put that on anybody if it's not
true. So, yeah. Um, a lot of people are
speculating that it was, you know, maybe
a man or a woman. I don't know. But, uh,
page six confirmed today that they are
indeed separated.
Uh it says um Angie Kay and her husband
of nearly three decades have separated.
They're not divorced. They're not
divorcing,
but they're separated right now. Uh
multiple sources told them uh that the
longtime couple are no longer together
romantically.
And uh let's see, it was something else.
They said more recently, eagleeyed
internet users, y'all know the Bravo fan
is crazy. The Bravo fan base, they are
detectives. They noticed that her
husband was following several divorce
related Instagram accounts, but he
insisted the activity had nothing to do
with Angie. Um, and then the husband
told uh Reality Shrine in January, "I
simply have someone close to me going
through a rough time. This person sends
me pages with thoughts and info on what
they are going through. It's as simple
as that. Nothing more, nothing less.
Queen Barlo is vindicated.
Sean is too boring to be gay.
Uh, so Lisa Barlo was right. I don't
remember
um Lisa saying anything about it, but I
don't know. Yes, she would. But then cuz
strife that would get her kicked off.
So then
uh I came across
Carlos King and Monica, remember her?
The one and done housewife.
Uh they like the Kiki now. And I'm
pretty sure they're going to be
recapping the show together. I don't
really care for Monica. She's quite the
pick me. She's a little um a little
touched in the head, too. So, I wouldn't
trust her around the cast. She's just a
weirdo, you know. So, uh this is what I
came across. This is fair use YouTube.
Fair use. I'm sure none of y'all a few
of y'all haven't come across this clip
of her and Carlos kiking about Angie's
situation. Listen up on it. I want to
tell you what I heard.
>> He heard something, y'all.
>> Tell me. I want to know if it aligns
with what I
>> Okay. I did not. Okay. And I'm being
very honest.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> I didn't hear about infidelity. I I
didn't hear it. I'm not saying it's true
or it's not true. I didn't hear that.
I did hear that
Shawn may allegedly feel
that Angie K has changed once she became
a housewife.
>> Why are you [laughter]
>> They are having
>> Exactly. When I heard this
>> they are having a she has become
She has become
>> unrecognizable,
>> intolerable, insufferable, difficult,
un uh out of touch with reality, uh
all consumed by the show. Maybe it's
kind of Look, Mother Mary said it best,
baby girl. She said, "You're letting
this [ __ ] get to your head." Mary said
it. Mary has been telling her season
after season, "You're changing. You're
changing. You're changing. You're
changing. I don't recognize you. I don't
know this one. I don't Where's my old
Angie friend?" D
>> I That's Yeah.
>> So, we heard the same thing.
>> We heard the same thing.
>> Um I I I did
>> child.
First off,
I I be trying with Carlos Kingch. I I be
trying.
Respectfully, like
it kind of rubbed me the wrong way that
they were taking delight in this tea,
especially Monica. And Monica to call
somebody insufferable and changing.
[ __ ] aren't you supposed to be in the
food stamp line right now? Take care of
your damn kids. How about that?
Like don't don't worry about her because
she'll be fine even without her man.
What are you doing right now?
Like what what is going on in your bank
account?
I'm I'm disgusted because it's just the
messengers. That's all. Like Carlo like
they are both clout chasers honestly.
And look, I get it. Carlos King now is a
YouTuber. He's doing great right now.
Bravo to you. Pun intended.
Like, you know, to be the next Andy
Cohen didn't work out for him. So, he
came down to YouTube with us to get the
bag. I get it.
But yeah, um
Monica needs to shut the [ __ ] up and
worry about her own situation because
Angie K will be fine regardless. You
still would want her life. Okay.
And yeah, um the T for as for the tea
itself, I can probably see that too
because I think in wife swap he seemed
like he was tired of Angie K, you know,
so I can see that. and he was probably
just tired of her or maybe like well
Angie K I could see her being fine with
things but her husband looked that there
was always always just a grimace to him.
So yeah, I feel bad for her and I'm
pretty sure we're going to see things
play out on the show. The editors are
going to have a field day. I know
they're going to have a field day.
They're probably going to be like
zooming in on um his facial reactions
and stuff like that. The reunions is
going to be a key. Watch what happens
live and stuff like that. So yeah. Um Oh
yeah.
I I remember his allegedly days. He
stopped. He definitely stopped when when
he was called out on it trying to take
allegedly. We all know where allegedly
came from. Like Alex already had an
allegedly song.
And here come this cigarette coming from
the shadows stealing people's [ __ ]
[clears throat] Get your own [ __ ] Why
you riding mine?
Thank you, Rich the Fish. 140 uh Dig
Riders. Oh my god. That is not going to
be my fan base name. The Dig Riders.
I see I just can't trust you being a
mod. You you you you too uh
unpredictable. Rich, we're celebrating
our babies Chris and Alex putting
together a soldout show. Thank you,
Biffas and Dig Riders.
That is not the official name for my fan
base. Thank you very much.
And yes, what what about Carlos's shows
do y'all hear about at all? by his
guests.
Bravo is paying his bills just like
Bravo paying mine.
Did he really say that?
At least Angie isn't on food.
He came to YouTube. Yep.
Yeah. Like Angie will be okay. I mean, I
think it's just sad because 27 years and
then also there's a child involved, too.
Even though she's a pre-teen, when when
parents divorce, when you're in pre-teen
ages, like 13, 14, it's fine. But when
you're in like
like your adolescent years and stuff
like that, pre-adolescent, single
digits, it kind of [ __ ] with you a
little bit.
Yeah. I I feel bad for Electra, but
going back to Carlos and uh Monica,
just wrong messengers. The the way
they're laughing and smiling and kiking
about the mess. And we already know how
Monica feels about the Salt Lake City
cast. She probably has voodoo dolls of
all these women like in a closet
somewhere.
But what what else do we know about um
Monica right now? Is anything else going
on with Monica? No, not at all.
I see y'all like that name, Dig Riders.
[sighs and gasps]
Anyway,
everyone lives off the teat of Bravo in
one way or another. Yep.
Yeah. like she just has a nasty spirit.
Like I don't really care for her. And
even though she followed me and I was
seeing it for her in the beginning of
the season, but as the season progressed
and we got to the finale and then the
reunion where she shot herself in the
foot was unapologetic for her actions at
all. Like it it's weird. It's weird. So,
however I feel about Jen Shaw, [ __ ] Jen
Shaw for one thing, but for you to be
camping out this woman's house,
following her, and then working for her,
too, and then um going to Heather's
business to get Botox before you were
even on the show. You were a fan of
these women. A fan infiltrated the show.
And then her obsession with Lisa Barlo
was also uh concerning as well. So yeah,
I don't know. I I just thought even
though
like they're giving the tea, Monica and
Carlos, I just didn't care for that
little opinion from them. But yeah, um
back to the news at hand. Angie K and
her husband separated. They have not yet
made a um an announcement on this. I'm
pretty sure we're gonna get it this
week. I I really do think so. Um I heard
from some sources that Angie Kay
definitely did not have a good season
and I think she's going to be the
villain. Unfortunately, it I heard it's
not a it's not a good season for Angie
as well as Brunwin.
So, it it's going to be something. And
hopefully they're back on the right
track because last season
didn't really care for it too much. Like
it started off strong but then the
season kind of tanked once Meredith and
that whole airplane debacle happened.
But we'll see what's going on. Now um
Salt Lake City officially has their big
story for every everybody to tune in.
I'm not sure PTOAC has that story yet,
but I'm pretty sure. Give it some time.
PTOAC is still filming, I believe.
Any other thoughts? Because this is a
Pop Quicky. Pop Quicky. Pop a Pop Quicky
episodes are going to be 30 minutes,
y'all.
Jen Shaw is no saint, but Monica is
obsessive. She is. She is dangerous.
Like, she will wear some of these ladies
skin.
Oh, well, it was inevitable. All fan
faves turn a villain inevitably.
I I can see that Monica was a stalker
and a weirdo. Exactly. Like these women
had to fear for their safety for someone
a fan to infiltrate their group like
that.
She's a fan. She's a fan. I forgot what
song that's from. Hopefully they can fix
it. Almost 30 years to be single again,
right?
But again, like you have your whole life
ahead of you. Why? Like I don't know. I
could do bad all by myself.
Monica is the epitome of single white
female.
And then her little black sense she
likes to use talking to Carlos King. I'm
sorry that this came this uh this topic
became me reading Carlos and Monica, but
I just can't stand their asses. That's
all.
Unfortunately, I'm not doing NextGen
this season. U maybe I'll talk about it
as a summary. I haven't even watched the
last episode and I heard Riley is not
doing well this season. Um, I also
heard, shout out to Brooke Ashley, that
at the Next Gen, this is a little T,
that at the Next Gen premiere, um, the
cast wasn't really [ __ ] with Riley
like that. And Riley was on the other
side of the room with her friends. She
wasn't really with the cast like that.
So, we might see, uh, Riley and Ariana
um, not be friends anymore. We'll see.
They already did the reunion.
I don't think it's gonna be that many
episodes either. It's going to be
probably like a cute eight weeks or so,
maybe 10.
Yeah, Ry's going to be fine. Candy is
her mom. Like, she's going to be fine as
well as her bank account.
I'm back. I almost forgot. Was nodding
off. Hey, Chris, congrats on the so sold
out show. Yes, it is a sold out show.
So, yeah, just because it's a soldout
show doesn't mean y'all can't watch it.
For the people who can't make it, we
have live stream tickets. It's an
unlimited supply of live stream tickets.
So, if you want to watch us be on stage,
it's a culmination of eight years doing
this together with Alex, you're not
going to want to miss it. It's going to
be a fun time. Uh the description uh the
in the description below is the link.
And also, if you are going to the show
and going to see us, get a meet and
greet ticket. We're going to be in the
back uh after the show. Key, you can get
your pictures and we can mingle a little
bit. So, yeah. Um
that's my topics, you know, for a little
pop quickie. Uh y'all have a a good
Monday evening. If you didn't check out
my Atlanta recap, go back and look at
it. Um but yeah, y'all, I'm I'mma head
out and finish my drink. With that, make
sure you like, comment, and subscribe.